《六人行》前情提要…
NARRATOR: Previously on Friends:
- 工作的事情谈得如何？ - 他给我一份工作
- How did the job stuff go?    - He offered me one!
你们知道吗？这该用以色列最高档香槟庆祝
You know what? This calls for a bottle of Israel's finest!
工作地点在巴黎
The job is in Paris.
天啊 拜托 谁说句话
Oh, God, please, somebody say something.
如果你接受这份工作 你就要搬到巴黎吗？
So if you take this job, you'll be moving to Paris?
或者是花时间在通勤上
Or facing a bitch of a commute.
我知道巴黎很大 很陌生 而且离你们很远
I know, it's huge, and it's scary and it's really far, far away from you guys.
但对我来说 这是很好的机会
But this is such an incredible opportunity for me.
我已经告诉他们 我们俩与艾玛的处境
And I've already told them about our situation with Emma.
他们说愿意满足我们的需求 尽量让我们觉得自在
And they said they'll do whatever we need to make us feel comfortable.
好吧
Okay.
我的意思是我可以两地飞行 或者他们让你飞去巴黎 什么都行
I mean, I'll fly back and forth, they'll fly you out. Anything we want.
我老板说我可以 在我的小隔间新添一盏灯
My boss said I might be getting a new lamp in my cubicle.
- 好吧 我们会想办法   - 谢谢你…
- All right. We'll work it out.     - Oh, thank you. Thank you.
耶
Yeah.
- 你确定这是你想要的吗？ - 我想是的
- You sure this is what you want?     - I think it is.
- 怎么回事？ - 我得到一份很棒的工作
- What's going on?     - I got a really incredible job offer.
- 太好了   - 我为你高兴
- Hey, great! All right!     - Good for you!
- 在巴黎工作   - 什么？
- It's in Paris.     - What?
不…太多变化了 好吗？
No, no, no! No, no, no! No, no, too much is changing, okay?
先是菲比结了婚 恭喜
First Phoebe getting married. Congratulations.
然后这两个人 要搬到愚蠢的郊区房子
And then these two move in to a stupid house in the stupid suburbs.
- 你之前说你会支持的   - 感觉来无影去无踪 说不准的
- Earlier, you said you'd be supportive.     - It comes and goes. I wouldn't trust it.
各位 这对我而言真的很重要
You guys, this is really, really important to me.
如果你们可以支持我 对我意义重大
It means a lot if you could try to get on board.
- 我们当然支持 恭喜   - 谢谢你
- Of course we can. Congratulations. Yay!     - Thank you.
- 乔伊？ - 不不
- Joey?    - No,no.No.
我的拥抱只留给待在美国的人
No, my hugs are reserved for people staying in America.
- 乔伊 那不代表…   - 嘿
- Joey, it would mean...     - Hey!
不 把你向法国弯的胳臂移开
No! Get your France-going arms away from me!
乔伊
RACHEL Joey.
- 你可以接受吗？ - 那让我觉得很难过 但是…
- Are you okay with this?     - Well, it makes me feel sad, but...
- 我是和罗斯讲话   - 了解
- Talking to Ross.     - I see.
瑞秋搬到另一个国家去？没有办法每天看到她？
Rachel moving to another country? Not being able to see her every day?
- 我怎么可能接受？ - 我知道
- How could I be okay with this?     - I know.
但是你要怎么做？她需要这份工作
But what are we gonna do? She really needs this job.
你觉得如果劳夫罗伦要她 再回去上班
Do you think if the Ralph Lauren people offered her her old job back...
她会接受吗？
...she would take it?
怎么可能？
How's that gonna happen?
现在是用掉三个神奇愿望 其中一个的好时机？
Is this the best way to use one of your three magic wishes?
我不知道 或许我可以和她上司谈
Like, I don't know, I could talk to her boss. Yeah.
我在圣诞派对上见过他 我们聊得挺愉快的
I met him at that Christmas party. I mean, we really hit it off.
- 那个一直叫你"罗恩"的家伙？ - 我没说我们情同兄弟
- The guy who kept calling you "Ron"?     - I didn't say we were brothers!
(中央咖啡厅)
- 嘿 菲比   - 嘿 你觉得如何
- Hey, Phoebe.     - Hey, tell me what you think.
我们要买的房子的 隔壁房子才刚要卖
The house next door to the one that we're buying just went on the market.
我想要看一看 但是钱德不肯
I wanna take a look at it, but Chandler doesn't.
明天公证托管就要结束了
We close escrow tomorrow.
多看一间房子只会混淆我们 我们很容易搞混的
Seeing another house can only confuse us. We're easily confused.
我们不是很聪明
We're not very bright.
但是如果比我们的房子好呢？我们不应该看一下吗？
But what if it's better than ours? Shouldn't we look?
菲比 你觉得呢？
What do you think, Pheebs?
我觉得那件衬衫让你看起来 像在"31冰淇淋"打工
Well, I think that shirt makes you look like you should work at a Baskin-Robbins.
随便啦…
Anyway...
- 乔伊的经纪人是伊斯特蕾欧娜吗？ - 是的
- Hey, isn't Joey's agent Estelle Leonard?     - Yeah.
- 她去世了   - 真的吗？
- She died.     - You're kidding.
- 太糟了   - 上周六去世的
- That's terrible.     - Yeah, last Saturday.
她是第一位独自飞行 横渡大西洋的黑人
Wow! She was the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic.
- 哦 等一下 我看错了   - 哦 是吗？
- Oh, wait a minute, I read the wrong one.     - Oh, yeah?
- 是的 她只是个经纪人   - 乔伊一定会很难过
- Yeah, she was just an agent.     - Joey's gonna be so upset.
没错 他一直都想要成为 第一位横渡大西洋的黑人
I know. He always wanted to be the first black man to cross the Atlantic.
我们不能告诉乔伊
We cannot tell Joey about this.
他已经受够所有的改变
He's already flipping out about everything that's changing.
那样会把他逼到死角
This will push him over the edge.
- 你觉得我们不应该告诉他吗？ - 先不要说
- You don't think we should tell him?     - Not for a while.
先给他几天的时间适应一切
Let's just give him a few days to get used to everything else.
要是他看到报纸呢？
What if he reads it in the paper?
除非史努比跟查理布朗说 我想我们是不用担心的
Unless Snoopy says it to Charlie Brown, I think we're okay.
- 有什么事吗？ - 是的 我是瑞秋葛林的朋友
- May I help you?     - Yeah. I'm a friend of Rachel Green's.
其实我们在两年前的 圣诞派对上见过面
Um, actually, we met at the Christmas party about two years ago.
- 对了 唐恩？ - 很接近了 罗恩
- Oh, right. Don?     - Close. Ron.
有什么我能帮得上忙？
Well, what can I do for you?
我来这里是想问你 能不能让瑞秋复职
Um, well, I'm here to see if you'll give Rachel her job back.
她请你来当说客吗？
Ah, did she ask you to come here and do this?
我要先获得你的同意…
No. First I have to get you to agree...
然后我们再去问她要不要回来
...then we'll see if she wants to come back.
真是吸引人
Wow, that is tempting.
她热爱这里的工作 坦白说 你不会找到任何人…
She loved her job here. Let's face it you're not gonna find anyone...
做得像她一样好 对不对？
...who did it as well as she did. Isn't that true?
- 她很出色   - 喔 我只是随口说说
- She is good.      - Huh. I took a shot there.
但是很抱歉 我无法做什么
But I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do.
事实上 是我不想做什么
Oh, that's not true. There's nothing I want to do.
我懂了
I see.
- 非常感谢   - 嗯
- Thanks very much.     - Mm-hm.
- 这是你的儿子吗？ - 是的 他叫罗斯
- Is this your son?     - Yeah, his name is Ross.
- 怎么了？ - 没什么 只是听起来和罗恩很像
- What?     - Nothing, it's just that it's close to Ron.
小罗斯会不会碰巧很喜欢恐龙？
Does he, um...? Does little Ross like dinosaurs, by any chance?
他常常提到恐龙 为什么问？
Yeah, they're all he talks about. Why?
他会不会想和我一起去 美国自然历史博物馆
How would he like to come with me to the Museum of Natural History...
大家都离馆后 只有我和他两人…
...after everyone else has left, just the two of us...
他可以想摸什么就摸什么
...and he can touch anything he wants?
我所说的与你听到的 一定会造成误解
I just heard it how you must have heard it, and that's not good.
我从头来过 我是古生物学家
Let me start again. I'm a paleontologist.
你会和我们一块去 只是触摸骨头…化石
You'll be there with us, and the touching refers only to bones... Fossils!
- 你真的能安排吗？ - 只要你让瑞秋复职
- You could really arrange that?     - You let Rachel come back and it's done.
我想让瑞秋回来 也不是世上最糟的事
Well, I guess having Rachel back wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
是啊 谢谢你 太好了 非常感谢
Yes! Thank you! This is great! Thank you so much.
我发誓你儿子一定会永生难忘的
I swear, your kid's gonna have the time of his life.
那就好 我很担心小罗斯
That's great. I worry about little Ross.
他老是看书 收集石头 而且非常迷恐龙
He's always reading, collecting rocks and he's obsessed with dinosaurs.
他会没事的
He'll be fine!
- 你好 菲比   - 你好
- Hey, Pheebs.     - Hey.
- 你没事吧   - 我在生我经纪人的气
- Everything okay?     - I'm just mad at my agent.
伊斯特？为什么？
Estelle? Why?
有个电视影集的角色很适合我
There's a part in this TV movie that I would be perfect for...
但我甚至没被安排试演 她最好要有个好理由
...and I didn't even get put up for it. She better have a good reason.
我想她有的
I'm guessing she does.
我要知道为什么 因为她老是这样
Well, I wanna hear it, because she keeps doing this.
不 等等…好 我得走了
No, wait, wait, wait! All right, I gotta go.
你听我说 答应我 你会等一下才打给她
Just listen. Promise me that you will wait a minute before you call her.
好的 为什么？
Well, Okay. Why?
因为朋友问的承诺 是不需要理由的
Because a promise between friends means never having to give a reason.
我喜欢那句谚语
I love that saying!
- 喂？ - 乔伊 我是伊斯特
- Hello?     - Joey, it's Estelle.
我正打算要找你 真奇怪
I was just gonna call you. That's weird.
有一点凑巧 却是可信的
It's a little coincidental, but believable.
听我说 我想你一定觉得奇怪 为什么我没有为你…
Listen, I'm sure you're wondering why I didn't get you...
安排那个电视影集的试演
...an audition for that TV movie.
是的 我觉得很怪
Yeah, actually I am.
我想那是我的失职
I guess I dropped the ball there. Whoopsie!
就这样？你最近似乎一直失职
That's it? You know, it seems like all you do lately is drop the ball.
不要用那种口气和我讲话 你以为你是谁？
Don't take that tone with me. Who do you think you are?
艾伦雷蒙 第一位独自飞行 横渡大西洋的黑人？
Alan Lemon, the first black man to fly solo across the Atlantic?
不 我要说的是 你是我的经纪人
No, look, all I'm saying is you're my agent...
你都不帮我争取试演 让我感到很厌烦
...and you're not getting me any auditions and I'm tired of it.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
我说这样行不通 好吗 伊斯特？
I'm saying that this isn't working for me anymore, okay, Estelle?
你被开除了 再见
You're fired. Goodbye.
天啊 伊斯特这周还真难熬
Man, tough week for Estelle.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.     - Hi.
艾玛把她的暴龙玩具留在我屋里
Um, Emma left her stuffed T. rex at my house.
- 没有这个 她睡不着觉   - 她已经睡着了
- You know she can't sleep without it.     - Ah. Well, she's asleep now.
- 不要强迫她接受那个   - 好的
- Stop forcing that thing on her.     - Okay.
你一定不会相信 我今天发生了什么事
Oh! You're not gonna believe what happened to me today!
劳夫罗伦打给我 要让我复职
Ralph Lauren called and gave me my job back.
- 不会吧   - 这真是太奇怪了
- No!     - I mean, it was the weirdest thing.
他们开除我 然后突然又要我复职
They fire me and then out of nowhere, they just hire me back.
那个公司少了我 一定是一团乱
I mean, that place must just be falling apart without me!
- 所以你不去巴黎了？ - 没有 我还是要去
- So you're not going to Paris?     - No, I'm still going.
什么？
What?
当路易威登的人得知…
Well, when the Louis Vuitton people found out...
劳夫罗伦要我回去上班 他们给我更高的薪水
...that Ralph Lauren wanted me back, they offered me more money!
罗斯 很棒吧
Ross, isn't that great?
呀
Yay!
你好 我们打算买隔壁的房子
Hi. We're buying the house next door...
我们可不可以进来看看？
...and we were wondering if we could take a look around?
当然 我正在带人参观 不过请进 随便看
I'm showing it to someone else, but please, look around.
谢谢
Thanks.
我觉得我们在背叛我们的房子
I feel like we're cheating on our house.
如果我们要背叛的话 也要找个年轻貌美的房子
If we're gonna cheat, shouldn't it be with a hot, younger house...
能提供我们房子没法提供的服务？
...that does stuff that our house won't do?
我们的房子好多了
Ours is so much better.
客厅比较小 餐厅看起来像个洞穴
This living room is smaller, the dining room looks like a cave.
真烂
What a hole!
- 你们觉得如何？ - 很喜欢
- So, what do you think?    - Loveit
已经有个买家出价了 我想楼上的太太也会出价
We already have one offer. I think the lady upstairs is gonna make another one.
他们可能会是我们的邻居 他们是什么样的人？
They could be our neighbors. What are they like?
楼上的太太人很好 她和她先生有两个小孩
The woman upstairs is nice. She and her husband have two kids.
- 先生在华尔街上班 而她是…   - 我的天
- Uh, he's on Wall Street, and she's a...     - Oh, my God!
当然
Sure.
嘿 乔伊 你要不要和我一起去…
Hey, Joey, you wanna come with me to...?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事 只是对开除伊斯特过意不去
Yeah, I just feel bad about firing Estelle.
一定会要她的命
This has gotta be killing her.
不 那不会要她的命
No, that wouldn't kill her.
冠状动脉栓塞才会
A coronary embolism might.
我不晓得 她一定很难受 我是她唯一的客户
I don't know. She's gotta be taking it hard. I was, like, her only client.
除了那个会吃纸的家伙
Except for this guy who eats paper.
我猜他吃下的钱 比他赚的还多
And I'm guessing he eats more money than he makes.
我知道她不是最棒的经纪人 但是她跟了我十年
Look, I know she's not a great agent, but she did stick with me for 10 years.
- 我要打给她 再雇用她   - 不…不要打给她
- I'm gonna call her and hire her again.     - No, no, no! Don't call her.
- 等她打给你   - 为什么？
- You wait for her to call you.    - Why?
因为耐心是谅解的不二法门
Because patience is the road to understanding.
谅解是开心的关键
Which is the key to a happy heart.
你让我飘飘然
You blow me away.
答应我 你等她打电话给你
All right, so promise you're gonna wait for her to call you?
- 我答应   - 好的
- I promise.     - Okay.
因为朋友间的承诺 是不需要理由的
And that means never having to give a reason.
世界真小
What a small world!
我就从来都没遇过碧昂丝
And yet I never run into Beyoncé.
你们彼此认识？
You two know each other?
陈年往事 在摩妮卡 把他变成一个老实人前…
Oh, we go way back. Before Monica made an honest man out of him...
钱德以前可是我的可爱小玛芬松糕
...Chandler used to be my little love muffin.
所以你们也打算买这栋房子吗？
So are you guys thinking of getting this house too?
我们将会有场竞标大战吗？得先警告你们 我可是个劲敌
Are we gonna have a bidding war? I better warn you, I'm a toughie.
不要…
Don't. Don't. Don't.
不是 其实我们是要买隔壁的房子
No, actually, we are buying the house next door.
为什么？
Why?
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
那我就决定了 我本来还在考虑
Oh, that decides it, then! I was on the fence.
但是知道你们将会成为我们的邻居
But knowing that you two would be our neighbors?
我们一定要买下来
Now we have to get it.
爱伦 我们得谈谈价钱
Ellen, we're gonna talk numbers.
绝对不能
This cannot be happening.
房地产经纪人说 还有另一对夫妻想买
Okay, the realtor said another couple made an offer.
或许珍妮丝夫妻不会得标 也许另一对夫妻会买到
Maybe the Janices won't get it! Maybe the other couple will.
除非那对夫妻是希特勒才有可能
The only way that that is going to happen is if the other couple are the Hitlers!
好…这样好了 我们何不买下两栋房子？
Okay, okay! All right, what if we get both houses?
- 我们可以把这里改成宾馆   - 真是个好主意
- We can turn this one into a guesthouse!     - That's a great idea!
顺便问一下 我不是要扫兴…
By the way, I don't mean to sound distasteful...
但你要上哪生钱？
...but when did you start crapping money?
- 那你来出主意   - 好吧
- You come up with an idea.     - All right.
我们房子的公证托管 还有三小时才会完成
We've still got three hours till escrow closes on our house.
- 我们还是可以不买   - 但是我们喜欢那栋房子
- We can still get out.     - But we love our house.
如果有她住在隔壁 我们还会这么喜欢吗？
Will we love it so much with her next door?
而且她在这里还是会很吵
And she's gonna be louder out here too!
不断地喊着"我…的…天"
Just the crickets and, "Oh, my God!"
好吧 但如果我们不买那栋房子 她还是会出其不意地出现
Okay. But if we don't get this house, she's still gonna show up wherever we go.
至少如果她住在这里 可以降低惊讶的程度
At least if she's here, it eliminates the element of surprise.
你就不会再听到那三个字
Never again will you have to hear the three words...
让你的蛋蛋在体内乱跳
...that make your balls jump back up inside your body!
我们得想办法 不能让她住在隔壁
Well, we have to do something. We can't have her living next door.
那也有同样的效果
Oh, that does it too.
哪位？
Who is it?
是我 罗恩
It's me. Ron.
我知道瑞秋拒绝了你
Look, I know Rachel turned you down...
但我想还是有办法 让她回来这里上班
...but I think there's a way you might be able to get her to come back.
可能会令你诧异 但我主要的工作 不是让解雇的人复职
This may surprise you, but rehiring fired employees is not my main job.
请听我说完
Just hear me out.
你觉得帮她加薪如何？
How would you feel about offering her a raise?
不好 罗恩
Not good, Ron.
或许我可以说服你
Perhaps I can persuade you.
如果我给你的儿子…
What if you could give your son...
这颗维妙维肖翼手龙蛋
...this genuine pterodactyl egg replica.
挺酷的
Wow. That's pretty cool.
怎么样？达成协议吗？
Huh? So? Do we have a deal?
- 成交   - 太好了
- Qkay, you got it.     - Yes! Yes!
- 这可是会让我大受欢迎   - 哦
- This is gonna make me very popular.     - Oh.
相信我 小姐们为之疯狂
Believe me, the ladies, they love it.
我指的是我儿子
I meant with my son.
那好 因为小姐们不是那么喜欢
Good, because the ladies, not so much.
乔伊 我是艾尔里布可
<i> Joey, this is AI Zebooker...</i>
吃纸的人
<i>...the guy who eats paper.</i>
我想你应该听说伊斯特过世了
<i>I'm sure you've heard that Estelle passed away.</i>
我想告诉你 有个为她举行的告别式
<i>I wanted to let you know there's a memorial for her...</i>
明天十点在西区礼拜堂
<i>...at the Westside Chapel tomorrow at 10.</i>
希望你能来
<i>Hope you can make it.</i>
我的天
Oh, my God.
- 喂？ - 乔伊 我是伊斯特
- Hello?     - Joey, it's Estelle.
伊斯特？
Estelle?
是的 我只是打来告诉你 你开除我 我不觉得难过
Yeah, I wanted to call and tell you that there's no hard feelings for firing me.
好的 我只是… 不相信你会打电话给我
Okay. I just... I can't believe you're calling me.
我想我不应该直接去拜访你
I didn't think I should just drop by.
不…不用来拜访…
No, no! Don't drop by! Don't drop by!
不…
No.No.No.
总之 你做了你应该做的事 我没事的
Anyway, you did what you had to do. I'm okay.
我可以问你一件事吗？
Can I ask you something? Um...
那里是什么样子的？
What's it like there?
还可以
It's all right.
老兄 我得走了
Look, kiddo, I gotta go.
祝你事业顺利 你一定会大红大紫
Good luck with the career. You're gonna be huge!
多谢 伊斯特 再见
Thanks for everything, Estelle. Bye.
"不在本区" 天啊 这还用说
"Out of area." Boy, I'll say.
我刚刚和席德谈过
Well, I just talked to Sid.
我们肯定要出价买这栋房子
We are definitely putting in an offer on the house.
我打赌我们一定会买到的
And I'll bet we get it!
希特勒一定会很失望
The Hitlers will be so disappointed.
好了 我得走了 帮我和摩妮卡说再见
All right, I gotta run. Tell Monica I say goodbye.
我们待会儿见 邻居
And I'll see you later, neighbor. Ha, ha.
等等
Wait!
我只是想让你知道 我很高兴你将要搬到这里
I just want you to know that I'm so happy you're going to be here.
我也是
Oh, me too.
因为…
Because...
如此一来
...that way...
我们就可以重新来过
...we can pick up where we left off.
- 哈？ - 我从来没有停止爱你
- Huh?  - I never stopped loving you.
- 我的…   - 好…
- Oh, my...     - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我想要你
I want you.
我需要你
I need you.
我要拥有你 珍妮丝里门葛洛琳荷森庭
I must have you, Janice Litman-Goralnik neé Hosenstein.
钱德 你在说什么？
Chandler, what are you talking about?
你将会住在隔壁 我们就可以每天见面
Now that you live next door, we can be together every day.
席德和摩妮卡将会被蒙在鼓里
Sid and Monica never have to know a thing.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
你知道的 很明显我们俩有热情
I mean, you know, obviously we have this heat between us.
很明显
Obviously.
但是我爱我先生
But I love my husband.
而且我知道你爱你太太
And I know you love your wife.
我想我们不能要这栋房子了
I don't think we should get this house now.
别那么说 别追求梦想 然后又把梦想带走
Don't say that. Don't dangle the dream and take it away.
钱德 我们其中一人得要坚强
Chandler, one of us has got to be strong.
我能了解
I understand.
虽然…
Although...
也许临别软弱一下无妨
Maybe just one last moment of weakness.
再见 钱德宾
Goodbye, Chandler Bing.
它们永远都不会再下来了
They're never coming down now!
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi.     - Hi!
你绝对不会相信 我今天发生了什么事
You are never going to believe what happened to me today.
什么？
What?
劳夫罗伦又打来 他们要给我更多的薪水
Ralph Lauren called, again, and they offered me more money.
- 是吗？ - 是的 真是十分古怪
- They did?   - Yes! It was the weirdest thing.
塞纳打给我 他说 只要你回来 我们不计任何代价
Zelner called me and said, "We will do anything we can to get you back."
而且我应该要谢谢一位叫罗恩的人
And that I should thank some "Ron."
我甚至不知道那个家伙在哪个部门
I don't even know what department that guy's in!
- 那你要怎么做？ - 我接受了
- So, what are you gonna do?     - Well, I took it!
太好了 所以你会留在纽约
That's great! So you're staying in New York!
- 你很开心吧   - 是
- You're excited, right?     - Yeah.
你知道的 薪水很好
Yeah, you know... Look, the money's great.
- 这个选择肯定比较容易   - 没错
- It's certainly the easier choice.     - Right.
不过 我期待去巴黎吗？那是一定的
But, you know, I mean, was I looking forward to going to Paris? Sure.
在世界流行之都工作 会让我觉得很兴奋吗？
You know, was I excited about working in the fashion capital of the world?
那还用说
Oh, absolutely.
哦
Oh...
是啊 不过你知道的…
Yeah, but you know, this is...
没有关系 我无所谓 回去做那份我差不多都…
It's fine. I'm fine going back to a job where I've pretty much...
已经摸熟弄透的工作
...gotten everything out of it that I possibly can.
我不晓得…
Um, I had really...
我不晓得你很期待去巴黎
I had no idea you were so excited about Paris.
你说你很担心
Um, I mean, you said you were scared.
那是好方面的担心 你懂吗？
Well, yeah, I mean, it was "good" scared, though, you know?
像是当我要搬到纽约的担心
I mean, like "when I moved to New York" scared.
或是当我发现 我怀了艾玛的那种担心
Or, uh, "when I found out I was gonna have Emma" scared.
但是没关系 这么做也很好
But this is fine. This is gonna be good.
你应该去巴黎
You should go.
什么？
What?
那是你想要的 你就应该去
It's what you want. You should go.
你真的这么认为？
You really think so?
真的
I really do.
但是我已经告诉塞纳 我要回去上班
But I already told Zelner that I would come back.
我想他会谅解的
I'm sure he'll understand.
好吧…我决定了 我要去巴黎
All right. All right! I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna go to Paris.
- 太好了   - 太好了
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
我要去巴黎了
I'm going to Paris!
- 谢谢你 罗斯   - 不客气…
- Thank you, Ross.     - Yeah, yeah.
哦
Oh.
我好开心
Oh, I'm so hapPY-
那我也很开心
Then I'm happy too.
成谢各位莅临
Thank you all for coming.
我们今天在此悼念 一位出色的经纪人
We're here today to pay our respects to a wonderful agent...
一位美丽的女士
...and a beautiful woman.
有内在美的女士
Inside.
身为伊斯特的唯二客户 我们有些话要说
As Estelle's only two clients, we would like to say a few words.
老兄 我的讲稿呢？
Dude, where's my speech?
真能博君一笑 各位 艾尔里布可
That is entertaining. Al Zebooker, everybody!